Kagiya's scent is so calming.
這就是鍵谷的味道，好讓人安心
It tickles.
好癢
I'm sorry.
對…對不起
I'm no good at this.
我果然不擅長這個
My gosh…
怎麼辦？
It feels so nice.
好舒服
Kagiya, uh…
鍵谷，那個…
Do you have one…?
你有那個嗎？
Huh?
呃？
Thank you for your purchase.
謝謝光臨
Hello.
喂
I'm sorry.
對不起
A client is having some urgent problem.
客戶好像出了緊急狀況
Oh, I see. You got called in.
這樣啊，你被叫過去了
I'm really sorry.
真的很抱歉
At this timing…
在這種時候
No, please go.
不會，你快去吧
You helped me before too.
你之前也幫過我
That evening when the copy machine broke.
之前晚上影印機壞掉時
You were my savior then.
你簡直就是救世主
Kosaka…
香坂
I'll wash your clothes and return them.
衣服我洗過後再還給你
No, you can just leave them. They'll be annoying to carry.
不用啦，放著就好 帶著走也很麻煩吧？
But…
但是…
Then let's meet the day after tomorrow.
不然，我們後天再見面吧？
I should be getting off work early that day.
我那天應該會早點下班
We could have hotpot here.
我們可以一起煮火鍋
Well, I'd need to buy a pot for it, but…
雖然沒有鍋子，得去買就是了
Uh, okay.
好
Well then…
那…
Take care.
路上小心
I'll be off.
我走了
ENERGY PARTNERS
（活力夥伴）
In short,
總而言之呢
Hara will be leaving us next month.
阿原下個月要離職了
What?
什麼？
Wait, what, since when?
等一下，我從來沒聽他提過啊
I'm sorry. It was sudden.
真的很抱歉，這麼突然
Too sudden…
也太突然…
He's changing jobs? To the largest company in the industry?
轉職？他要去大公司嗎？
I broke up with her.
我跟她分手了
I'm probably asexual.
我有可能是無性戀
I guess he's had a lot to think about since then.
他在那之後，可能也想了很多吧
Excuse me for a bit.
我離開一下
I recommended you to take over my position.
我推薦你接手我的位置了
Huh?
咦？
You're good at what you do. You should aim higher.
香坂你很能幹，目標應該要放高一點
I will be back next week.
我下週會再過來
I'm sure Kosaka would like something like this.
香坂感覺會喜歡這個
TWO PERSON USE 3800 YEN
（1到2人用，3800元）
Thank you very much.
謝謝光臨
I ended up just buying it.
自作主張買了
I hope she'll like it.
不曉得她會不會喜歡？
I'm sorry.
對不起
I will have to cancel tomorrow.
明天得取消了
"I've been made leader of a new project…"
“被指定當新專案的領導人”
THAT'S A SHAME
（真可惜）
THAT'S AMAZING DO YOUR BEST
（好厲害，加油吧）
MAIKO KOSAKA
（香坂麻衣子）
I need to work hard too.
我也得更努力才行
He's so handsome.
好帥喔
Do you think he's a model?
他是模特兒嗎？
Can you believe someone this handsome wanted a second date with me?
沒想到能跟這樣的帥哥再一次約會
Sorry for the sudden message. I got tickets for an event at DOPE.
不好意思這麼突然 我有DOPE活動的票
Want to go tonight?
今晚要不要來？
Keita…
啓太啊…
How dare he think I'll come running as soon as he asks?
是說他以為只要約我，我就會去嗎？
Sorry, I'm with someone so I can't. I probably won't have time for a while.
抱歉，我正在和別人見面 可能有段時間會沒空
Hey, Ren.
我說，小蓮
Are you busy later?
你等一下有空嗎？
No, not at all.
嗯，我都沒事
Come on.
天啊
Why did Hara leave me with such a big project?
為什麼阿原 要留這麼大的案子給我啊？
I was supposed to be seeing Kagiya tonight.
今晚本來要跟鍵谷見面的
I want to call him.
好想打給他
Can I?
可以嗎？
I can, right?
可以吧？
We are dating after all.
畢竟我們在交往了
No.
不
We aren't yet.
我們還沒交往
We haven't even had sex yet.
我們也還沒上床
I wonder how many times I've re-read these.
我重複看了幾次呢？
My conversations with Kosaka.
我和香坂的對話
I've never thought about anyone this much.
這是第一次 我竟然會這麼想念一個人
I'm happy but…
雖然很開心
I feel worried because I have no confidence in myself.
但也很不安，我對自己很沒自信
I can't help
像這樣的我
but find it hard to believe that she would stay with someone like me.
她應該不會想一直和我在一起吧？
But I…
但是我…
like her.
喜歡她
CERTIFICATIONS
（證照）
Okay, done for today.
好，今天的部分完成了
Huh? Kagiya?
咦？鍵谷？
Hello.
喂
Kosaka. Is now a good time?
香坂，現在方便講電話嗎？
Sure.
可以
Is something wrong?
怎麼了嗎？
Umm…
那個…
Do you want to go to a museum this weekend?
方便的話 這週末要不要一起去美術館？
Huh? A museum?
咦？美術館？
I was given tickets by that client from the other night.
之前發生問題的客戶送了票給我
As a thank you.
說是當作謝禮
That night?
那天晚上的嗎？
Yes, I really want to go.
我要去，我一定要去
I'll look at all the paintings.
我要把畫都看一遍
Okay.
那先這樣
Um.
我說
This is the first time, isn't it?
這是第一次，對吧？
That you ask me out.
你來邀我出去
Oh.
對喔
I'll invite you to a lot more things from now on.
今後我會多邀你的
Okay.
好
Yeah, it's fine.
好，沒事了
We haven't officially asked each other out,
雖然沒有正式說要在一起
or had sex yet,
也還沒有上床
but I'm sure it's fine.
但一定沒問題的
Do you often go out around here?
你很常來這附近嗎？
That place just now was so pretty.
剛才那個地方很漂亮
You think so? I'm glad.
真的嗎？太好了
I could easily spend all night with Touya.
跟東也在一起的話 玩到天亮都沒問題
Yo.
唷
What? Are you kidding me?
什麼鬼？真的假的？
Let's go, shall we?
我們走吧？
That place lets us go in as three.
那邊可以三個人一起進去
What?
什麼？
Huh?
咦？
Have you never had a threesome before?
小蓮你是第一次嗎？三個人一起做？
Hey.
喂
Dude, are you blind?
我說你有長眼睛嗎？
I'm not. It's fine.
當然有啊，好的很
I never said anyone would do.
我可沒說過誰都行啊
I can't believe you.
開什麼玩笑啊
Then…
那麼…
Ren, do you want to ask a friend to join?
小蓮，叫你的朋友一起…
Huh?
哎呀？
What's up with her?
什麼嘛
She isn't cute at all.
她一點都不可愛啊
I figured it would be good to mix it up every now and then.
我想說偶爾換換類型也不錯啊
Yes, of course that's what it was.
沒錯，果然又是這樣
I knew that. I knew, but…
我知道的
But I was hoping it would be different this time.
但我還是希望這次會不一樣
Why?
為什麼？
Why does this happen to me just because I'm not pretty?
為什麼只是長得不可愛 就要遭受這種對待？
Ren!
蓮
Oh no! Without thinking I…
討厭，我不自覺地…
I'm glad.
太好了
Let's go together.
我們一起去吧？
I said I wasn't coming.
我明明就說了不去
I acted so selfish…
明明擺出那麼自私的態度
So why is he still so nice?
為什麼還是對我這麼好？
Hey.
喂
Hmm?
怎麼了？
Why do you want to keep seeing me?
你為什麼想見我？
Why are you so nice?
為什麼要對我這麼好？
I'm ugly.
我長得這麼醜
What happened?
發生什麼事了？
Something awful.
發生了很討厭的事情
You…
你…
Always laugh at my stories.
總是對我說的話，笑得很開心吧？
It makes me so happy.
那樣讓我覺得很高興
I can't talk to anyone else about music like this,
我沒有遇過能這樣聊音樂的人
so that's why I'm seeing you.
所以才想見你
Because it's fun.
因為很快樂
And you're cool.
而且你很酷啊
Like the singer in D.Pool.
就像D.Pool的主唱一樣
Thanks.
謝謝
Let's go.
走吧
You're changing my assigned area?
要更換我的負責區域嗎？
Yes.
對
The conditions on your new contract changed a bit.
這次的續約條件有點變化
I just figured out the ins and outs here.
我想說好不容易比較適應了
I know, but it's the condition of the new contract.
我懂你的心情，但續約條件就是這樣
Alright, we're done!
好，完成了！
Should we go tonight, then?
那我們今晚一起去吧？
-To celebrate Kosaka's promotion. -No, it's your farewell party.
-慶祝香坂升職了 -拜託，是你的送別會才對吧？
-Of course! -Thank you!
-對啊 -謝謝你
Ms. Misono, will you come too?
味園小姐，你要來嗎？
-Of course. -I'm glad.
-當然啊 -我好高興
Oh, we're getting on.
啊，我們要搭電梯
Can we fit?
擠得下嗎？
I really have nothing to offer.
我真的是一無所有呢
Kagiya.
鍵谷
Kosaka.
香坂
Huh?
嗯？
Did something happen?
發生什麼事情了嗎？
You seem down.
你看起來很沒精神
No.
沒有
That was wonderful. The use of colors.
這些顏色搭配真漂亮呢
Yes.
對啊
Art styles really change with different eras.
畫風真的是會隨著年代改變呢
It started out quite concrete, but then became more abstract, didn't it?
一開始是很具體 然後變得越來越抽象，對吧？
We noticed the same things.
我們注意到一樣的地方呢
Do you like sweets?
你喜歡甜食嗎？
Huh?
什麼？
Oh. Yeah.
喔，對啊
How about you?
你呢？
Me too.
我也是
Are you a dog-person?
那你是狗派嗎？
Good question.
怎麼說呢？
I liked the stray cats that lived around my parents' housing complex.
老家附近有很多流浪貓，我蠻喜歡的
Then you're a cat-person.
那就是貓派了吧？
I'm definitely a dog-person.
我是徹底的狗派
Though lately I find cats cute too.
不過最近覺得貓也很可愛
Whereabouts do you live?
你家住哪裡呢？
I live in Ota city.
我住在大田區
Why all the questions all of a sudden?
話說，突然問這些是怎麼了？
I want to know more about you.
我想要多瞭解你
Because I didn't know anything until now.
我之前對你完全不瞭解
Kosaka…
香坂
I'm sorry.
抱歉
I wanted to pay.
本來應該是我要付錢的
Not at all.
不會啦
You got the tickets for us.
你準備了門票嘛
UNPARALLELED SHOGI PLAYER FUJIMOTO SNACKED ON THEM DURING THE GAME
（藤本三冠在對弈中吃的點心）
How about we go over there?
我們去那邊吧？
Huh?
什麼？
Oh.
喔
It's okay.
沒關係的
I feel better than before.
我覺得比之前好多了
I feel worse about making you worry.
讓你這麼顧慮我，真是不好意思
Actually, Kosaka.
比起這件事，香坂
I'm being assigned a different area at work.
我接下來要換負責區域了
What? Really?
咦？是喔？
Yes.
對
I see…
這樣啊
That's sad.
有點寂寞呢
It's fine though, right?
不過，沒關係的吧？
I mean, you and I…
因為我們…
… are dating, right?
正在交往吧？
W-We can still see each other.
我們還會再見面吧？
Why is he not replying?
他為什麼不說話？
Maiko!
麻衣子
Yuri.
友里
Didn't expect to run into you here.
沒想到會在這裡遇到你
Same to you.
真的
Are you shopping?
你出來買東西嗎？
Yeah, my husband is taking care of the kids.
對，我老公在顧小孩
Is this your boyfriend?
那是你男朋友嗎？
Huh?
什麼？
Hello. I've known Maiko for a long time.
你好，麻衣子受你照顧了
Hello.
你好
You're wrong.
不是啦
He's not my boyfriend.
他不是男朋友啦
Stop, right now. He's going to feel uncomfortable.
快結束這個話題 不然鍵谷會覺得不舒服的
Oh, I see. Sorry for bothering you.
這樣啊，抱歉打擾了
See you.
再見囉
I'm sorry. She's an old classmate.
抱歉，她是我同學
She's always been like that.
從以前她就是那個樣子
Kagiya…
鍵谷
Something is wrong, right?
果然有發生什麼事，對吧？
You don't seem happy today at all.
你今天感覺很不開心
No, not at all.
沒有
Want to go look at the stores over there?
我們去那裡逛逛吧？
I wanted us to have hotpot together soon, remember?
我說過下次要煮火鍋吧？
So I need to buy a pot.
所以得買鍋子才行
Do you…
香坂
even have fun when you're with me?
跟像我這樣的人在一起開心嗎？
Huh?
什麼？
Don't you think someone else would be better?
如果不是我會更好嗎？
What are you talking about…
鍵谷，你在說什麼…
Please tell me how you feel.
請告訴我你的感覺
Do you hate me?
你已經討厭我了嗎？
I was wrong. I should have told you.
我錯了，我應該先告訴你的
I love you.
我喜歡你，香坂
I love you too.
我也喜歡你
I'm actually going to do it with Kagiya.
我真的要和鍵谷做了